

Frolov Evgenii

Male, 25 years, born on 11 October 1996

+7 (960) 4506021

evg.frolov777@gmail.com — preferred means of communication

Another site: https://t.me/slenter777

Reside in: Rostov-na-Donu

Citizenship: Russia, work permit at: Russia Ready to relocate, ready for rare business trips

Desired position and salary

Frontend developer

3 000

Specializations:

Programmer, developer

Employment: full time

Work schedule: remote working Desired travel time to work: any

Work experience — 2 years 3 months

December 2021
— till now
10 months

Impress

Spain, smile2impress.com/

Medicine, Pharmaceuticals, Pharmacies

- Pharmaceutical Products (Production)
- Pharmaceutical Products (Promotion, Wholesale)

Frontend-developer

- Development of medical products on React, Redux, TypeScript, Redux Observable and Node.JS;
- Developing UI library;
- Writing e2e or unit tests;
- Configuring CI/CD;
- Showing a demonstration of the work done;
- Supporting doctors in chat, here we needed to tell about our product and how is it works;
- Work on improving the project architecture;

April 2021 — December 2021 9 months

Сбербанк

Rostov-na-Donu, www.sbrf.ru

Financial Sector

Banking

Software engineer

- Engaged developing micro-applications on React, Redux, TypeScript and Redux Observable;
- Working on a UI components library;
- Configuring project deployment;
- Supporting other developers;

October 2020 — April 2021 7 months

ZUZEX

Rostov-na-Donu, www.zuzex.com/

IT, System Integration, Internet

- Internet Company (Search Engines, Payment Systems, Social Networks, Information and Educational, Entertainment Resources, Website Promotion etc.)
- Software Development

• System Integration, Technological and Business Processes Automation, IT Consulting

Software engineer

- Developing the SPA front-end with Next.js and React + Redux;
- Developing back-end with Nest.JS + MongoDB

May 2020 — July 2020 3 months

uKit Group

Rostov-na-Donu, ukit.com

HTML-верстальщик

Creating mockups on website constructor.

Education

Incomplete higher

2016

DGAU

Technology of production and processing of agricultural products, Bioltechnology

Key skills

Languages

Russian — Native

English — B1 — Intermediate German — A2 — Elementary

Skills

TypeScript JavaScript React Redux Webpack Node.js Rx.Js
Redux observable Git Nest.Js CI/CD

Further information

About me

Throughout my career I have worked with various technologies, but most of the time I have been creating applications using React.JS , Redux and Typescript. I also have experience with Node.JS and Nest.JS. I don't like a routine, so I try to automate it. I like to improve work efficiency and, first of all, focus on the end user of the product.